[
  {
    "question": "Someone call __________ police!",
    "correct": 2,
    "options": ["a", "an", "the", "No article"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The plane flew _______ us.",
    "correct": 3,
    "options": ["by", "on", "beyond", "over"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It was time to be stood on her own two feet.",
    "correct": 1,
    "options": ["stood", "stand", "be standing", "standing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Only if I had known about her intentions before, I __________ alert.",
    "correct": 0,
    "options": ["would have been", "will had been", "will have been", "would had been"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In consider the difficulties of his position, he has acted admiralty.",
    "correct": 3,
    "options": [
      "Considering of the difficulties",
      "Considering to the difficulties",
      "In considering to the difficulties",
      "Considering the difficulties",
      "No error"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After carefully reading both the books, the editor and her colleague found that the only difference between them were their names.",
    "correct": 3,
    "options": [
      "them were the names",
      "these was their names",
      "the books was their names",
      "the books were their names",
      "No error"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "John dropped his wallet coming out from the shop.",
    "correct": 1,
    "options": [
      "John dropped the wallet coming out from the shop",
      "While coming out of the shop, John dropped his wallet",
      "Wallet coming out of the shop was dropped by John",
      "While coming out of the shop, the wallet was dropped by John",
      "No error"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct synonym for the following word: Expressive",
    "correct": 2,
    "options": ["Garrulous", "Incoherent", "Articulate", "Verbose"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct antonym for the following word: Chivalrous",
    "correct": 1,
    "options": ["Virile", "Despicable", "Gallant", "Mannish"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct antonym for the following word: Oblivion",
    "correct": 0,
    "options": ["Alert", "Comely", "Indifferent", "Bijou"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct spelling of the word to fill in the blank: The best part of my daily ____ is to wake up early.",
    "correct": 3,
    "options": ["ruotene", "routene", "ruotine", "routine"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rearrange the given phrases to form a complete sentence. Note: The phrases numbered 1 and 6 are fixed. Yet so few of us have (A) walls of daily routine (B) the time or the means (C) that enclose our lives (D) to break through the narrow 6. to get to know this land",
    "correct": 2,
    "options": ["BDCA", "ABDC", "BDAC", "DBAC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rearrange the given phrases to form a complete sentence. Note: The phrases numbered 1 and 6 are fixed. Effective writing involves (A) careful choice of words, their organization (B) in the correct order to (C) well as cohesive composition (D) form sentences, as 6. of sentences.",
    "correct": 1,
    "options": ["ABCD", "ABDC", "CDAB", "BACD"]
  }
]
